hotforwords.com 2009-12-28

# Privacy Policy

### **Ownership of Information**

HotForWords, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on the HotForWords website.

### **Mailing List**

HotForWords, LLC offers a free subscription to the HotForWords website. When you sign up to the HotForWords website, you may receive from time to time an email of an eCard (holiday email from HotForWords) as well as notifications of replies to comments you make on the website.  In order to sign up to receive regular emails from any website, users must submit information including a valid email address.

Users who choose to sign up for this site will receive these special holiday cards, or other specials, and separately, if users sign up for the new post notifications on the upper right corner of the site, they will also receive notifications when new posts are made on the site. These services are independent of each other, and a user can exist in either service, or both. If you do not wish to receive emails from HotForWords, you can [unsubscribe at any time.](http://www.hotforwords.com/subscribe/ "Subscription")

### **Third Party Cookies**

Some of our advertisers may use cookies on our site, such as Google Adwords, etc. However, HotForWords, LLC has no access to or control over these cookies, as they are a common feature of advertising on any website. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by the HotForWords website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### **Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the HotForWords website. These companies may use information (which DOES NOT include your name or email address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### **Log Files**

Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

### **Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, HotForWords, LLC may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on the HotForWords website.

### **Business Transitions**

In the event HotForWords, LLC or HotForWords.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred, but the same Privacy Policy will most likely be in effect.

### **Links**

The HotForWords website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that HotForWords, LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. HotForWords.com encourages its users to be aware when they leave its site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the HotForWords website.

### **Notification of Changes**

Whenever the HotForWords website changes its privacy policy, the changes will be posted to this privacy statement, and other places deemed appropriate.

### **Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.hotforwords.com/support "contact us").
